<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Blog</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/09/my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/09/my-blog/</guid>
      <description>The Power of R and Python Semester Update Honestly, I was nervous about taking computational biology. The idea of making a website at the end of the course made me even more nervous. However, I enjoyed Biostats, and I was interested in taking another coding course. Seeing that the course fit my degree plan, I registered. Now, it is December! Wow! Another semester complete! My journey in SDS348 was not smooth sailing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Birth Weight dataset examines various attributes of mothers and their new born infants. It contains 7 variables: the infant&#39;s birth weight in ounces, the infant&#39;s gestation period in days, the infant&#39;s parity (first born = 1, later birth = 0), the mother&#39;s age in years, mother&#39;s height in inches, mother&#39;s weight in pounds, and whether the mother smokes (1=yes, 0=no). The dataset contains 1174 observations. The data was originally acquired from the Child Health and Development Studies conducted at the Kaiser Foundation Hospital on Oakland, California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDS348: Project 1 Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration  Introduction The datasets I have chosen inspect two unique sets of characteristics about each state of the United States. The US Arrest dataset examines the rates of various violent crimes in 1973, as well as the percentage of the population living in urban areas. It contains 4 variables: murder, assault, rape, and UrbanPop, and these variables are measured per 100,000 people. The data was acquired from the World Almanac and Book of Facts (1975) by researcher D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
